Rajat Kumar Bhuyarkar

 ♥ Bhopal, India
 ■ rajatbhuyarkar2023@gmail.com
 □ 9399828802
 ■ in/rajat-kumar-bhuyarkar

SUMMARY

Project Manager and Business Development Executive with 1 year of experience, specializing in generating business leads and facilitating smooth communication through scheduling meetings. Effectively utilized project management skills to develop detailed project plans, gather stakeholder requirements, create work breakdown structures, and establish milestones; successfully hosted stakeholder meetings from initial project charters to execution and monitoring phases.

EXPERIENCE

Project Manager & Business Development Executive

iifetech Pvt. Ltd.

August 2024 - October 2024, Bhopal

- · Actively Contributing to generating business leads.
- · Scheduling meetings and facilitating smooth communication.
- Utilized Project to develop detailed project plans; gather requirements from project stakeholders, developed efficient work breakdown structures and established reasonable milestones.

Business Analyst

Agnito Technology PVT. LTD.

January 2024 - June 2024, Bhopal

- · Capable of effectively communicate in a complex, cross-functional and geographically dispersed stakeholders · and team members.
- · Wrote requirement documents such as BRD, FRD, SRS, DFD, MOM, RTM, User stories, Use Cases, and more followed by IEEE standards.
- · Created Prototypes/Wireframes and DFD/ER diagrams.
- · Participated in Sprint Planning meetings to initiate the task flow and responsibilities.
- · I worked as a Business Development Executive on platforms such as Freelancer, wellfound, Upwork, and LinkedIn.
- I worked as a UI/UX designer (Software Figma) enhancing user interface aesthetics and experience by designing and prototyping feature updates in Figma.
- · Brainstorming, Project Management, Business Analyst Process.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ SWOT Analysis , Manual Functional Testing .
- \cdot Agile/Scrum Methodologies , Gap Analysis.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER PROGRAM

Coding Thinkers

July 2023 - January 2024, Bhopal

SKILLS

Java, HTML:5, CSS, Javascript, SQL, Draw.io, Trello, Powerpoint, Microsoft Office, PowerBI, Project Management, Staff Augmentation

PROJECTS

Stepout Helper For Elder

• Stepout Helper For Elder is a Electric bike built on a simple philosophy to make urban mobility seamless & sustainable what started off as an initiative for disable and old age people.

CAR TRAFFIC MANIA

- Car traffic Mania platform is a virtual gaming applications designed to provide users with an exhilarating racing experience for players . players can control a car navigating through a challenging course while avoiding collisions with other cars approaching from the front .
- · Created UI/UX design of the game.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology

Sagar Institute of Science and Technology Gandhinagar Bhopal (M.P.) · Bhopal · 2023

· Percentage - 83.90%(Academic Topper)

CERTIFICATIONS

Electric Vehicle Startup Conclave (EVSC)

Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya, Bhopal (M.P.)